http://www.ciena.com/about/corporate-governance/privacy-policy/

Skip Content
There was a problem with your video. Another version is available.
Privacy policy
Privacy policy
This privacy policy (the Policy) sets out how we, at Ciena, collect, use and protect your personal information.
We can collect your personal information when you:
browse our web site(s);
subscribe to our alerts and publications (including newsletters and mailing lists);
request information from us about products and services;
contact us with a question or complaint;
visit us at various industry events
Collecting & Using Personal Information
The information we may collect includes, but isn’t limited to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address. You can use our website without divulging any personal information. We do not collect personal information about you unless you expressly provide such information to us on a voluntary basis, for example, when registering or logging into our Community or Customer Portal, subscribing to our investor distribution or one of our publications, downloading a White Paper, attending a webinar, or requesting more information to be sent to you about Ciena. We will only use your personal information for the purposes that you have provided it for or consented to.
Our commitment to data security
To prevent unauthorized access and misuse of your personal information (including accidental loss, disclosure, alteration or destruction), maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate technical, organizational, administrative, physical and procedural security measures to safeguard and secure the information that we collect from you as described in this Policy.
We do not rent, sell, or share the personal information we collect about you with third parties or non-affiliated companies, unless we are required to by law, or in response to a government investigation.
To the extent that third parties assist Ciena in the provision of our website(s) or services offered on our website(s) (or otherwise), those third parties have no independent rights to your personal information, we make sure they have appropriate protections in place for your personal information, and only process your personal information in the way we have permitted them to.
Non-Personal and aggregated information collected automatically
When you visit our website, we log general data, such as your domain name, the name of the web page from which you entered our website, which pages you visit on our website, and how much time you spend on each page. We use this information to monitor use of and improve our website as well as for internal analysis. In particular, we use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the website, and gather information for aggregate use (IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information).
Use of Cookies
Our website uses "cookies" to help personalize your online experience, such as recognizing repeat visitors. A cookie is a text file that is anonymously placed on your hard disk by a web page server. This site's cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. Ciena does not match your personally identifiable information with the cookie assigned to you without your permission. We will not share or sell non-aggregated information contained within cookies with any third party. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of our website or receive some of our services.
External links
Ciena may provide links to external web sites for your convenience. The links and information these sites contain are not monitored by us and those sites are subject to their own privacy policies. We are not responsible for the content, accuracy or practices of these sites nor do we endorse these sites or content provide thereon.
Changes to the Policy
The date set out at the end of this Policy indicates the date it was last updated. We may occasionally amend this Policy to reflect company and customer feedback and any changes in applicable data protection and privacy legislation.
We encourage you to periodically review this Policy to be informed of how we are committed to protecting your information and providing you with improved content on our website. If we make any material changes in the way we collect, use, and/or share the personal information that you have voluntarily provided, we will notify you by posting notice of the changes at this Policy. By using this website, you signify your agreement with the terms of this Privacy.
Data Retention
We retain personal information we collect from you where we have an ongoing legitimate business need to do so (for example, to provide you with a service you have requested or to comply with applicable legal, tax or accounting requirements).
When we have no ongoing legitimate business need to process your personal information, we will either delete or anonymize it or, if this is not possible (for example, because your personal information has been stored in backup archives), then we will securely store your personal information and isolate it from any further processing until deletion is possible.
Questions about our privacy policy and contacting Ciena
If you have any questions about this Policy, please contact us by email at: privacypolicy@ciena.com. Or by writing to Ciena at:
Ciena CorporationATTN: Director of Digital Marketing7035 Ridge Road, Hanover, Maryland 21076, USA
If you wish to unsubscribe or discontinue receiving communications from us (including newsletters and other materials) please use the unsubscribe facility/preference center link provided here. If you wish to update your information, please contact us by email at privacypolicy@ciena.com or at the contact information above.
Data Protection Rights
For the purposes of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), the California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) and other relevant data protection or privacy legislation, Ciena is the Data Controller of your personal data.
Pursuant to such data protection or privacy legislations, you have the right to ask Ciena via email at privacypolicy@ciena.com for a copy of your personal data; to correct, delete or restrict processing of your personal data; and to obtain the personal data you provided to us in a structured, machine readable format . You have the right to withdraw your consent to our use of your personal data at any time. If you have unresolved concerns, you have the right to complain to the relevant data protection authority.
Legal Notice
For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, “Ciena” means Ciena Corporation, and any company or other entity which Ciena Corporation owns (directly or indirectly) 100% of the issued share capital. If the business is sold or integrated with another business, your details may be disclosed to our advisers and any prospective purchaser’s adviser(s) and will be passed to the new owners of the business. Where required by local law, you will be informed of such transfers.
March 2020
Unchecking this box will prevent you from subscribing to Ciena's communications.
Can we help you answer a question?
Questions?
Yes
No
Are you a current Ciena customer?
Yes No/ Not sure
Do you need support on an existing product?
Yes No
We're happy to help!
Visit our community Contact support
Do you want to learn more about Ciena's products?
Yes No
Here's some useful information
Connect with Ciena Learn more about us
Do you want to learn more about Ciena's products?
Yes No
Do you need support on an existing product?
Yes No
Here's some useful information
Connect with Ciena Learn more about us
Subscribe now for the latest Network Insights.
Subscribe
I agree to subscribe to Ciena's communications. I understand I can unsubscribe at any time.
I agree to subscribe to Ciena's communications. I understand I can unsubscribe at any time.
Back
Thank you! You have subscribed successfully.
Blue Planet Multi-Domain Service Orchestration (MDSO)
Blue Planet NFV Orchestration
Blue Planet Route Optimization and Analysis
Blue Planet Inventory
Manage, Control and Plan (MCP)
A network that grows smarter, more agile, and more responsive EVERY DAY
We build networks that are ‘fit for flexibility’ today, and into the future. Learn about who we are and what we do.
Blue Planet Multi-Domain Service Orchestration (MDSO)
Blue Planet NFV Orchestration
Blue Planet Route Optimization and Analysis
Blue Planet Inventory
Manage, Control and Plan (MCP)
We build networks that are ‘fit for flexibility’ today, and into the future. Learn about who we are and what we do.
Loading static suggestions...
Static suggestion error.
No static suggestions.
Additional searches
Loading organic suggestions...
Organic suggestion error.
No organic suggestions.
